[{"id": 2763, "question": "What is the color1 of the universe? Astronomers had not answered this question until two months ago. That is when two American astronomers reported on their study of all the light in the universe. They said that the universe would appear to the human eyes to be a light greenish color1. Karl Glazebrook and Ivan Baldry of Johns Hopkins University in Baltimore, Maryland, reported their finding in January. They presented the research at a meeting of the American Astronomical Society. They said that finding the color1 of the universe was not part of their more serious scientific research. They did it for fun. However, earlier this month, the scientists admitted making a mistake. They said their finding was much more color1ful than it should have been. They now say the light from our universe is...\n\nQ: The color1 of the universe is   _  .", "options": ["close to white", "black", "blue", "light greenish"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 811, "question": "If you like bicycling as much as you like playing ball and can't seem to decide between the two sports, you may want to consider cycle ball--a fun sport that adopts the key attributes from both activities and transforms it into a totally new game.. Also known as red ball, the game was invented in 1893 by German laborers who wished to play polo , but could not afford horses. While the sport has not _ in North America, it is very fashionable in Europe and even Japan. Played in an indoor court, cycle ball is similar to soccer in many ways--the aim is to score as many goals as possible, and only the goalkeeper is allowed to touch the ball. The one big difference? Use of legs is forbidden. Instead, players have to guide the ball across the court, using the front wheels of their bicycles or with...\n\nQ: Which of the following is TRUE according to the text?", "options": ["Cycle ball is popular both in Japan and other Asian countries.", "The cycle ball game is popular all over the world.", "A cycle ball game takes 14 minutes.", "Cycle ball has to be played with heads, legs or the front wheels."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1374, "question": "Nowadays more and more people are talking about genetically modified foods ( GM foods). GM foods develop from genetically modified organisms , which have had specific changes introduced into their DNA by genetic engineering techniques. These techniques are much more precise where an organism is exposed to chemicals to create a nonspecific but stable change. For many people, the hightech production raises all kinds of environmental, ethical, health and safety problems. Particularly in countries with long farming traditions, the idea seems against nature. In fact, GM foods are already very much a part of our lives. They were first put on the market in 1996. A third of the corn and more than half the cotton grown in the U. S. last year was the product of biotechnology, according to the Depart...\n\nQ: According to the passage, GM foods  _  .", "options": ["will replace naturally grown foods", "are far better than naturally grown foods", "may help to solve the problem of poor nutrition", "can cause serious trouble in developing countries"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1967, "question": "Here is some general information about Edison Elementary School. For more information, you can visit our website which is printed on the cover. Attendance: Please contact the office at 480. 472. 5282 if your child is going to be absent. Renaissance Reading: The Accelerated Reader (AR) Program is a computerized reading enrichment program that combines great children's literature with computer skills. As an individualized reading program, it is designed to motivate students to read more and to read good literature. Students of different abilities can use this program. It is not a competitive program but one that improves any student's reading ability. Here is how it works. Students select books in their reading range from our Accelerated Reader Selection and read it at their own pace. Once t...\n\nQ: It can be inferred from the passage that   _  .", "options": ["students won't be punished if they don't pass the quiz", "students only have one chance to test on a book", "students won't be praised if they reach their goals", "parents meet the teachers once a term"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1533, "question": "Postcards to myself In 50 years of traveling Colin McCorpuodale has visited every country in the world, except three.And everywhere he goes,he sends himself a postcard.He always chooses a postcard with a beautiful view,and sticks on an interesting stamp.Usually he writes just a short message to himself.His latest one,from the Malians island,read Good fishing. On a wall in his home in London there is a large map of the world.There are hundreds of little red pins stuck in it.\"It's good to get a pin in the map,\" says Mr.McCorquodale, \"but I follow the rules.I'm allowed to stick one in only if I've been in a place for more than 24 hours.\" Naturally,Mr.McCorpuodale has his favorite places.New Zealand he describes as\"wonderful\".In Europe,he says,\"Italy is a favorite place.But in Italy tourists a...\n\nQ: What is written on his latest postcard?", "options": ["A favorite place", "Malians island", "Good fishing", "A beautiful view"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 34, "question": "Hi, everybody! Welcome to our newly-opened Richards Cinema Bookstore! Now let me introduce to you some of the new film books in our store. Are you Chinese film fans? OK, here comes the latest 25 New Takes about Chinese films. It is a collection of 25 fresh readings of different Chinese films from the 1930s to the present. In recent years, Chinese films are very popular in the States, such as Crouching Tiger and Hidden Dragon, Hero, and Flowers of Shanghai. Do you like French films? Well, here is The French Cinema Book. It covers French films from the 1890s to the beginning of the 21st century. It is written for all lovers of French cinema: students and teachers, specialists and fans, and so on. Maybe you are Indian film fans and star-chasers. Then here is Encyclopedia of Indian Cinema. The...\n\nQ: The speaker of the passage is most probably   _  .", "options": ["the author of 25 New Takes", "a tourist in the cinema bookstore", "the manager of the cinema bookstore", "a reader of Encyclopedia of Indian Cinema"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1551, "question": "City Varieties The Headrow, Leeds. Tel. 430808 Oct 10-11 only A Night at the Varieties.All the fun of an old music hall with Barry Cryer, Duggle Brown, 6 dancers, Mystina, Jon Barker, Anne Dural and the Tony Harrison Trio. Laugh again at the old jokes and listen to your favourite songs. Performances: 8 pm nightly. Admission: L5; under 16 or over 60: L4. York Theatre Royal prefix = st1 /St Leonard's Place, York. Tel. 223568 Sept 23- Oct 17 Groping for Words-- a comedy by Sue Townsend. Best known for her Adrian Mole Diaries, Townsend now writes about an evening class, which two men and a woman attend. A gentle comedy. Admission: First night, Mon: L2; Tues- Fri: L3.25 - 5.50; Sat: L3.50 - 5.75. Halifax Playhouse King's Cross Street, Halifax. Tel. 365998 Oct 10-17 On Golden Pondby Ernest Thomp...\n\nQ: Which theatre offers the cheapest seat?", "options": ["Halifax Playhouse.", "City Varieties.", "Grand Theatre.", "York Theatre Royal."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 655, "question": "Many people have influence on my life, based on their personal characteristics, achievements, and values. I have been lucky to have had a great many teachers and professors who I respect for their patience and intelligence. There are artists who have encouraged me by their talents and creativity. I value many political leaders, who have inspired me by their contributions to society, and their ability to change our futures. But of all the people I have known in my life, the person I admire most is my father. As the youngest girl in my family, I always considered myself to be \"Daddy's little girl\". While I grew up, it always made me sad to see so many of my friends and neighbors without a father or father-like figure around. This helped me appreciate how my father always takes an interest in...\n\nQ: Which of the following could NOT be used to describe the author's father?", "options": ["Caring and humorous.", "Knowledgeable and sociable.", "Sympathetic and open-minded.", "Energetic and helpful."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1278, "question": "In 1974, after filling out fifty applications, going through four interviews, and winning one offer, I took what I could get ----- a teaching job at what I considered a distant wild area: western New Jersey. My characteristic optimism was alive only when I reminded myself that I would be doing what I had wanted to do since I was fourteen ------- teaching English. School started, but I felt more and more as if I were in a foreign country. Was this rural area really New Jersey? My students took a week off when hunting season began. I was told they were also frequently absent in late October to help their fathers make hay on the farms. I was a young woman from New York City, who thought that \"Make hay while the sun shines\" just meant to have a good time. But, still, I was teaching English. I ...\n\nQ: Which of the following gives the writer a sense of mild victory?", "options": ["Her talk about symbolism sounded convincing.", "She managed to finish the class without crying.", "Her students behaved a little better than usual.", "She was invited for a talk by her boss after class."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1843, "question": "SYDNEY--Australia's economic boom is encouraging a steady stream of unexpected visitors looking for work: Americans. U.S. citizens are heading to Australia in small but growing numbers as near-10% unemployment at home drives more to look for jobs Down Under, where China's thirst for iron ore and energy is transforming the Pacific nation into an economic powerhouse. A bricklaying student from Silver Trowel, a leading provider of quality education and training in the building and construction industry, apprentices on a building project in Western Australia, where workers are in short supply. Daniel Davila, a 23-year-old floorer from Camarillo, California made the 14-hour move across the Pacific two years ago. He had been forced to take a job stocking shelves at a local grocery store for $8.9...\n\nQ: _  , a growing number of Americans go to work in Australia.", "options": ["As a result of the encouragement of Australia", "As a result of high unemployment in the U.S.", "Out of their ambition of finding valuable resources", "Out of their determination to realize their dreams"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 88, "question": "When was the last time someone did something unexpectedly nice for you? Not someone you knew, but a total stranger? It's happened to me a few times, but two instances really stand out. A few years ago, I was dining out with a person who kept going on and on about himself, completely unaware of the fact that I was sitting there in misery . It wasn't his company that disappointed me. I was recovering from a bad grade in my study. I could have collapsed in tears right there at the table. When we picked up the check, the waitress said, \"Your meal was already paid for.\" My friend and I didn't have a clue how it happened. Then I remembered a man coming in out of the corner of my eye. He was dressed in mostly white, sat down at the bar, had a glass of wine, stayed for maybe ten minutes and then l...\n\nQ: Which of the following is the best title for the passage?", "options": ["The Kindness of Strangers", "An Unpleasant Friend", "Two Unbelievable Experiences", "Hitting the Wall"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1877, "question": "It's fun to receive presents. It also feels good to give presents to others. So what's the best way to budget your money, shop wisely and spend smartly this holiday season? Time for kids asked for advice from Susan Beacham of Money Savvy Generation, a company that teaches money-management skills to kids. \" My first tip is to make a list and check it twice,\" says Beacham. She suggests that kids talk with their families about whom to include in their gift giving and how much to spend. Start by writing down names, Beacham says. Then put a dollar amount next to each name and add it up. Do you have enough money? If not, make changes. And don't forget---- not everyone needs a store-bought gift. Beacham points out that some of the best presents are free. Add to your list the names of people you w...\n\nQ: What's the text mainly about?", "options": ["How to teach kids money-management skills.", "How to make plans for giving presents.", "How to do the math while shopping.", "How to make gifts from the heart."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 3106, "question": "When I was 18, I had a motorbike accident that put me in a coma for three months. The doctors said there was little chance of my coming out of it, but my identical twin, Marcus, didn't believe them and carried on talking to me. My first words when I came to myself were, \"Hello, Marcus. \"Even though I had no memory of my own name, or that the woman crying at my bedside was my mother, I knew Marcus immediately; it was like a genetic memory. just felt close to him. As weeks went by, I still could remember nothing before the accident. Marcus was the only person I could relate to. I had to relearn everything, and Marcus helped me. Because of my twin I wasn't scared of having lost my memory; I believed everything he said. He became my memory, telling me about my school, friends, previous girlfri...\n\nQ: What was the author's purpose in writing the text?", "options": ["To tell us the importance of being honest.", "To explain the meaning of success.", "To express his gratitude to his twin.", "To show how he had suffered."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 610, "question": "Sir Steven Redgrave Winner of 5 Olympic Gold Medals \"In 1997 I was found to have developed diabetes . Believing my career was over, I felt extremely low. Then one of the specialists said there was no reason why I should stop training and competing. That was it -- the encouragement I needed. I could still be a winner if I believed in myself. I am not saying that it isn't difficult sometimes. But I wanted to prove to myself that I wasn't finished yet. Nothing is to stand in my way.\" Karen Pickering Swimming World Champion \"I swim 4 hours a day, 6 days a week. I manage that sort of workload by putting it on top of my diary. This is the key to success -- you can't follow a career in any field without being well-organized. List what you believe you can achieve. Trust yourself, write down your g...\n\nQ: According to the passage, what do the three people have in common?", "options": ["Courage.", "Self-confidence.", "Devotion.", "Hard work."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2390, "question": "Here are some of the best movies you like. I believe they can accompany you to spend your dull weekend. In this story a computer hacker searches for the truth behind the mysterious force . In the 22nd century it turns out that the world is controlled by a magic computer system called the Matrix and people live in an unreal world. The computer hacker and his comrades overcome much difficulty and at last find the way to take over the Matrix and save the world. This comedy is about J and K, agents in a top secret agency , and they fight bravely with the alien to save the galaxy from a bad-tempered alien \"bug\" and save the Earth from being destroyed . Harry has lived under the stairs at his aunt and uncle's house. But on his 11th birthday, he learns he's a powerful wizard----with a place waiti...\n\nQ: The author writes the passage in order to    _   .", "options": ["let readers know more about the latest movies", "increase the income of the cinemas of the city", "tell readers some interesting summaries of movies", "help readers to choose the best movie they like"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2587, "question": "Elizabeth Mitchell's new \"Liberty's Torch\" is the fascinating story of how the Statue of Liberty came to be. The Statue of Liberty's rough history is explored in \"Liberty's Torch\". Frederic Auguste Bartholdi is an all-but-forgotten figure in American history. He was, however, responsible for one of the most enduring symbols of the United States: the Statue of Liberty. A Frenchman from Alsace, he designed and built the Statue of Liberty which stood on Bedloe's Island in New York Harbor. How this statue came to be is the fascinating subject of Elizabeth Michell's new book \"Liberty's Torch\". The power of Mitchell's narrative is convincing . We recognize the Statue of Liberty now as a symbol of hope and opportunity for a nation of immigrants. At the time, though, people could not see that-nor ...\n\nQ: It can be inferred from the text that   _  .", "options": ["American people have never forgotten Frederic August Bartholdi", "the Statue of Liberty wasn't originally regarded as a symbol of hope", "Bartholdi finished the Suez Canal", "Bartholdi was a famous architect from Egypt."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1301, "question": "The latest fashion in kitchen is the food steamer. All the stores are selling them; everyone wants one. Steaming is one of the simplest and healthiest ways of cooking food.However, that cooking time is usually longer than with other methods. In case you're thinking of buying a steamer, I've done a survey about the steamers available on the market to help you decide which will suit you best. *Folding Steamer The simplest and least expensive is the folding stainless-steel version. Advantages: This is a good, basic design which sits inside a variety of different shapes of pans with the water under it; a ring in the center allows for easy lifting and it's easy to clean. Disadvantages: It only holds small dishes. Also, if you put too much water in the pan, it will boil up through the vegetables...\n\nQ: According to the author, you should  _  .", "options": ["use steamers to save cooking time", "buy a steamer with dishes supplied", "do a survey before choosing a steamer", "buy a folding steamer if you want to try"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 725, "question": "Many people write to newspapers and magazines to express their opinions. Letters to the editor must carry the writer's full name, address and telephone number, although the information is not necessary for publication. This requirement to provide personal particulars is a clear indication that writers are responsible for what they say. When a writer wants his voice heard, he needs to claim ownership of his voice. Responsibility is the name of the game. \"People today prefer living together to putting their signatures on a marriage certificate because they refuse to accept responsibility for the relationship,\" said social worker Ken Yip, \"and this is what is causing a lot of family problems.\" When we sign a paper, for example, a business contract or a bank document, the signature is a seal o...\n\nQ: The passage is mainly about  _  .", "options": ["honor and writers", "signature and responsibility", "identity and signature", "anonymity and signature"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2439, "question": "It is a reply to a letter written by Zhai Mingjun, a 16-year-old girl in the class. The two astronauts thank the student for her concerns and wish the class luck in their future studies. \"I' m so happy that the two space men replied with a few encouraging words,\" said Zhai. Her letter was one of the 10 winning letters taken into space by Fei and Nie, who have succeeded in traveling space in the Sixth Shenzhou Spaceship. Zhai wrote the letter as if she were a younger sister of the astronauts. \"As the single child in my family, I always hoped that I would have an elder brother that I could be proud of,\" Zhai said. \"I thought that the astronauts would be lonely during such a long space trip. I hoped they would feel happy and warm when reading my letter.\" Many of Zhai' s classmates also wrote ...\n\nQ: What can you conclude from the passage?", "options": ["All the students look forward to China' s later space program", "Astronauts feel lonely during such a long space trip", "There is no gravity in the spaceship", "A composition con test had been held before the spaceship was launched"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2396, "question": "There's a guy like me in every state and federal prison in America,I guess--I'm the guy who can get these for you:cigarettes,a bag of cigar,if you want that,a bottle of wine to celebrate your son or daughter's high school graduation,or almost anything else...within reason,that is.It wasn't always that way. I came to Shawshank when I was just twenty,and I am one of the few people in the prison who is willing to admit what he did.I committed murder.I put a large insurance policy on my wife,who was three years older than 1 was,and then I fixed the brakes of the car her father had given us as a wedding present.It worked out exactly as I had planned,except I hadn't planned on her stopping to pick up the neighbour woman and the woman's son on the way down Castle Hill and into town.The brakes let...\n\nQ: The man committed such an evil crime because  _  .", "options": ["he had made a secret deal with an insurance company", "he had been angry for a long time with his father--in--law", "his wife's family members had disapproved of their marriage", "his wife had looked on him as a pet and he didn't feel respected"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 527, "question": "Are you having too much salt? You might not think so, but people in China eat on average about 12 grams of salt each day, that is much higher than the 6 grams suggested by the World Health Organization. You could be eating too much without realizing it, because about 75% of the salt we eat is already in the food we buy, such as bread, sauces, soups and sausages. What problems can eating too much salt cause? To answer that question, first let's take a look at what salt is. Salt is a chemical compound. It is made of sodium and chloride . Salt is used to keep and flavor foods. A small amount of salt is important for good health because our bodies need sodium and chloride to work. But past studies have found that people who eat more salt than they need tend to have high blood pressure. Eating ...\n\nQ: Many people in China don't realize they are eating too much salt because   _  .", "options": ["salty food tasted better than reduced salt food", "they do not calculate the amount of salt they eat", "about 3/4 of the salt we eat is already in the food we buy", "few people experience problems from eating too much salt"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2153, "question": "With thousands of waterfalls across the world, it is difficult to choose the best but the following list contains some of the world's most amazing and beautiful ones! Iguazu Falls-The Iguazu Falls is located on the border of Brazil and Argentina and it is well-known for its scenic beauty. Though it is just about 89 meters high, it ranks as the fourth best waterfall in the world because of its beauty. The U-shaped cliff in the waterfall which is known as the Devil's throat is the most striking feature of the waterfall. Angel Falls-The Angel Falls, named after its discoverer James Crawford Angel, is the world's highest waterfalls, falling from a height of 979 meters. It is located in the Bolivar state in Venezuela. A unique feature of the falls is that most of the water falling down gets blo...\n\nQ: What's the author's purpose of writing the text?", "options": ["To introduce some world famous waterfalls.", "To advise readers to pay a visit to these famous waterfalls.", "To explain how waterfalls came into being.", "To tell readers where these famous waterfalls are located."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 3016, "question": "We might not be alone in the universe. Actually, it may be confirmed as a very crowded place by new computer models developed to help identify habitable planets. Estimates of places where life can exist have been based on the possibility of them having surface water. But software recently developed by the Aberdeen University allows researchers to identify planets with underground water kept liquid by heat from planets. Water is fundamental for life and planets too close to the sun lose water to the atmosphere through evaporation. On the other hand, planets located in distant reaches from their star have their surface water locked away as ice. Sean McMahon, who is carrying out the work, explained: \"Traditionally people have said that if a planet is in this Goldilocks zone--not too hot and n...\n\nQ: What can we know about the computer models?", "options": ["They will help identify planets where there is life.", "They will help researchers find Goldilocks zones.", "They have helped find some significant discoveries.", "They have already located some habitats for life."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 665, "question": "A treasure trove hidden for centuries has been discovered in the underground vaults of a temple in southern India. The treasures include gold, diamonds and precious stones. The estimated value of the hoard is reportedly 22 billion US dollars. Hundreds of armed police have been deployed around the temple. Meanwhile, a debate about how to use the money has also broken out across the country. After discovering the treasure trove in Sri Padmanabhaswamy Temple in the southern Indian state of Kerala, the local government has assured security of the temple. Elaborating on the security arrangements, Venugopalan Nair, Additional Director General of the Kerala Police, says the latest security devices are being used to guard the temple. Venugopalan Nair, Additional Dir. Gen. of Kerala Police, said, \"...\n\nQ: How will the government deal with the treasure mentioned in the passage?", "options": ["It will be used to pay for poverty alleviation.", "It will be returned to its owner.", "It will be kept in the vaults.", "It hasn't been decided yet."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2580, "question": "Just five one-hundredths of an inch thick, light golden in color1 and with a perfect \"saddle curl,\" the Lay's potato chip seems an unlikely weapon for global domination. But its maker, Frito-Lay, thinks otherwise. \"Potato chips are a snack food for the world,\" said Salman Amin, the company's head of global marketing. Amin believes there is no corner of the world that can resist the charms of a Frito-Lay potato chip. Frito-Lay is the biggest snack maker in prefix = st1 /Americaowned by PepsiCo and accounts for over half of the parent company's $3 billion annual profits. But theU.S.snack food market is largely saturated, and to grow the company has to look overseas. Its strategy rests on two beliefs: first a global product offers economies of scale with which local brands cannot compete. And...\n\nQ: Frito-Lay's executives claim that the promoting of American food in the international market  _  .", "options": ["won't affect the eating habits of the local people", "will lead to economic imperialism", "will be in the interest of the local people", "won't spoil the taste of their chips"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1910, "question": "The ancient whistled language of the small island of La Gomera, off the coast of Africa, is about to disappear because of new technology and globalization. Now, a web company has taken on the task of saving the language by marrying history with technology. Silbo Gomero, a language used only on La Gomera Island, sounds to the untrained ear like few other known languages. The sounds that make up this language are made by whistling, rather than by speaking. The language was brought to the island by African setters many centuries ago. To communicate among the _ populated inland hills and valleys, shepherds had to use the whistled language, which could be heard and understood over distances of up to eight kilometers, compared to about 200 meters for a spoken word. With the development of new te...\n\nQ: What would be the best title for the passage?", "options": ["Africa suffers from new technology.", "Niesner and his website.", "Web company helps to save an ancient language.", "Silbo Gomero, a fun language."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1242, "question": "When my friend went to Europe last summer, instead of snapping photographs of the Louvre or the Eiffel Tower or Stonehenge, she brought back 32 rolls of ... cathedral ceilings. Ceilings. For the 10 years I've known her I had never suspected that she was this passionate about stained glass. Still one of the best things about such pictures -- despite their obvious narrow appeal -- is that they can't help but tell us a great deal about the people who took them. So I shouldn't have been surprised when I got the roll of film back from my 5-year-old son's first camping trip. I opened the envelope, naively expecting to see pictures of the nightly campfire, the sun setting over the forest, and possibly even a deer or two. Instead, I saw an off-center picture of tennis shoes. Not even his tennis sh...\n\nQ: Who might have taken a picture of the back seat of the family car in his or her trip mentioned in this passage?", "options": ["The author's friend.", "The author's son.", "The author.", "The author's friend's daughter."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2914, "question": "Most young people enjoy some forms of physical activities. It may be walking, cycling or swimming, or in winter, skating or skiing. It may be a game of some kind, football, hockey, golf, or tennis, it may be mountaineering. Those who have a passion for climbing high and difficult mountains are often looked upon with astonishment. Why are men and women willing to suffer cold and hardship, and to take risks on high mountaineering? This astonishment is caused probably by the difference between mountaineering and other forms of activity to which men give their leisure. Mountaineering is a sport and not a game. There are no manmade rules, as there are for such game as golf and football. There are, of course, rules of a different kind, which would be dangerous to ignore, but it is this freedom f...\n\nQ: Mountaineering is also a team sport because   _  .", "options": ["it involves rules as well", "it involves matches between teams", "mountaineers depend on each other while climbing", "it requires mental and physical qualifications"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 3096, "question": "The U.S. Department of Labor statistics show that there is an oversupply of college trained workers and that this oversupply is increasing. Already there have been more than enough teachers, engineers, physicists, aerospace experts, and other specialists. Yet colleges and graduate schools continue every year to turn out highly trained people to compete for jobs that aren't there. The result is that graduates cannot enter the professions for which they were trained and must take temporary jobs which do not require a college degree. On the other hand, there is a great need for skilled workers of all sorts: carpenters, electricians, mechanics, plumbers, TV repairmen. These people have more work than they can deal with, and their annual incomes are often higher than those of college graduates....\n\nQ: By saying that \"many people go to college who do not belong there\", the author means that   _  .", "options": ["many people who are not fit for college education go to college", "many people who do not have enough money go to college", "many people who go to college drop out within the first year", "many people who go to college have their hopes destroyed"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1201, "question": "It is under the CPC's leadership that China has overcome many challenges in its economic, political and social systems and achieved remarkable progress the world has ever seen. Under the CPC's leadership, China has become the world's largest second largest economy. People's lives have greatly improved, and hundreds of millions of people have been lifted out of poverty, an objective fact no one can deny. At the same time, China is quickly becoming a major player on the world stage. As a responsible nation, China has been playing a growing role and shouldered greater responsibilities in world affairs. Such achievements, especially for a nation with a size equaling to a continent and a population of nearly 1.4 billion, are not easy to make. What roles do you think CPC has played in China? Do ...\n\nQ: What's the best title for this passage?", "options": ["What roles do you think CPC plays in China?", "Why has CPC played an important role in China?", "China has become the world's second largest economy.", "China has overcome many challenges and achieved remarkable progress."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2019, "question": "If you are thinking of putting your child in a private high school instead of a public one, you should do some research. You will find that most private schools offer some advantages. One of the most important details of a good high school is small class size. Many public schools might have 30 or even 35 students in each class. However, many private schools limit the size to about 15 to 20 kids per class. This is a good thing because it allows each teacher to offer every student more attention. Another thing to mention is the interesting classes. For example, while the typical high school might only offer Spanish and French as foreign languages, private schools often have several other languages to choose from. This is especially important if your child is actually interested in studying a...\n\nQ: According to the text, colleges might like to choose students who     .", "options": ["live close to colleges", "have interest in sports", "have wide knowledge", "come from public high schools"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2552, "question": "More than 4 in 10 cancers -- 600,000 in the UK alone -- could be prevented if people led healthier lives, say experts. The population of the UK is about 63,000,000. Latest figures from Cancer Research UK show smoking is the biggest avoidable risk factor , followed by unhealthy diets. The charity advises people to live healthily, limit alcohol intake and do regular exercise. According to the figures from 2007 to 2011, more than 300,000 cases of cancer recorded were linked to smoking. A further 145,000 were linked to unhealthy diets containing too much processed food. Obesity contributed to 88,000 cases and alcohol to 62,200. Sun damage to the skin and physical inactivity were also contributing factors. Professor Max Parkin, a Cancer Research UK statistician, says, \"There's now little doubt ...\n\nQ: What's the main idea of the text?", "options": ["Most cancers are caused by smoking.", "Cancer is greatly linked to our lifestyle.", "There are different factors that lead to cancer.", "Public awareness should be raised to prevent cancer."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 190, "question": "Boys' schools are the perfect place to teach young men to express their emotions and involve them in activities such as art, dance and music. Far from the traditional image of a culture of aggressive masculinity ,the absence of girls gives boys the chance to develop without pressure to be consistent to a stereotype ,a US study says. Boys at single-sex schools were said to be more likely to get involved in cultural and artistic activities that helped develop their abilities to express their emotions,rather than feeling they had to obey to the\"boy code\"of hiding their emotions to be a\"real man\". The findings of the study are against the received wisdom that boys do better when taught alongside girls. Tony Little,headmaster of Eton,warned that boys were being ignored by the British education ...\n\nQ: What does Tony Little say about the British education system?", "options": ["It fails more boys than girls academically.", "It focuses more on mixed school education.", "It fails to give boys the attention they need.", "It places more pressure on boys than on girls."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 729, "question": "The adder is the only poisonous snake native to Britain. Adders have the most highly developed poison injecting mechanism of all snakes, but they are not aggressive animals. Adders will only use their poison as a last means of defence, usually if caught or trodden on. No one has died from adder bites in Britain for over 20 years. By faar the most common smake in Britain is the adder. In Scotland, in fact, there are no other snakes at all. The adder is also the only British sanke with a poisonous bite. It can be found almost anywhere, but prefers sunny hillsides and rough open country, including high gournd. In Ireland there are no snakes at all. Most people regard snake bites as a fatal misfortune, but not all bites are serious, and very few are fatal . Sometimes attempts at emergency trea...\n\nQ: Where are adders to be found?", "options": ["In fertile fields in Scotland.", "On wild land throughout Britain.", "In many parts of Britain and Ireland.", "Everywhere in Britian except Scotland"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 153, "question": "As the train approached the seaside town where I was going to spend my holiday, I went into the corridor to stretch my legs.I stayed there for a short while,breathing in the fresh air and exchanging a few words with one of the passengers,whom I had met earlier on the station platform. When I turned to go back to my seat,I happened to glance into the compartment next to mine.Sitting there was a man who many years before had been my neighbor.He was a great talker, I remembered;it used to take hours to get away from him once he began talking.I was not at all sorry when he went to live in another part of London.We had not met since then,nor did I wish to meet him now, when my holiday was about to begin. Luckily at that moment he was much too busy talking to the man opposite him to have the cha...\n\nQ: This story is about a man who_.", "options": ["got off the train to avoid meeting an ex-neighbor.", "went with an ex-neighbor to spend holiday at the seaside*", "tried to get away from an ex-neighbor but did not succeed*", "was surprised to meet his ex--neighbor in a small hotel*"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1381, "question": "One day a father and his rich family took his son on a trip to the country with the firm purpose to show him how poor people can be. They spent a day and a night on the farm of a very poor family. When they got back from their trip, the father asked his son, \"How was the trip?\" \"Very good, Dad!\" \"Did you see how poor people can be?\" the father asked. \"Yeah!\" \"And what did you learn?\" The son answered, \"I saw that we have a dog at home, and they have four. We have a pool that reaches to the middle of the garden; they have a creek that has no end. We have imported lamps in the garden; they have the stars. Our patio reaches to the front yard; they have a whole horizon.\" When the little boy finished, his father was speechless. The son added, \"Thanks, Dad, for showing me how poor we are!\" Isn't...\n\nQ: After the boy finished his words, his father was_.", "options": ["happy", "satisfied", "annoyed", "embarrassed"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 9, "question": "Little Tommy was doing very badly in math. His parents had tried everything--tutors, cards, special learning centers--in short, everything they could think of. Finally they took Tommy to a catholic school. After the first day, little Tommy came home with a very serious look on his face. He didn't kiss his mother hello. Instead, he went straight to his room and started studying. Books and papers were spread out all over the room and little Tommy was hard at work. His mother was surprised. She called him down to dinner and as soon as he finished eating, he went back to his room, without a word. In no time he was back hitting the books as hard as before. This went on for some time, day after day while the mother tried to understand what was happening. Finally, little Tommy brought home his re...\n\nQ: From the passage, we can infer that  _  .", "options": ["teachers should be strict with their students", "mistakes might do good sometimes", "a catholic school is much better than other ones", "nuns are good at helping children with their math"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2974, "question": "Most Americans receive at least two or three credit card applications in the mail every month.Why have credit cards become so popular? For a merchant, the answer is obvious.By putting charge slips in a bank, the merchant can change credit card sales into cash.In return for processing the merchant's credit card transactions , the bank charges a fee that ranges between 1.5 and 5 percent. The easiest way to establish credit is to open checking and savings accounts at your local bank.Then apply for a gasoline or store credit card.These cards are fairly easy to get because retailers want you to buy their goods and services.The third step, and the most dangerous one, is obtaining a major credit card like Visa, MasterCard, or American Express. It is important to choose a credit card carefully bec...\n\nQ: How does the merchant change credit card sales into cash ?", "options": ["With the help of Consumer Credit Counseling Service.", "By opening a checking and savings account at the local bank.", "By giving the bank the authority to charge.", "By mailing the customer's credit card to the bank."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 325, "question": "How will you celebrate New Year's Eve? By having a party with your classmates? Going to the karaoke for a singing competition? Many people around the world celebrate the day. Let's have a look at what people in other countries do. In the United States, thousands of people jam into Times Square in New York to welcome in the new year at midnight. The change from New Year's Eve and New Year's Day is very exciting. People count down the seconds to welcome the new day as the New Year ball slowly gets down and lights up the area. In Spain, when the clock strikes midnight, everyone eats 12 grapes. They eat one grape for each toll to bring good luck for the next 12 months of the new year. In Scotland, fireworks are set off in front of the Edinburgh Castle. Immediately after midnight, people sing A...\n\nQ: What's the best title of the passage?", "options": ["The history of New Year.", "New Year joy all around the world.", "Where to celebrate the New Year's Eve.", "12 grapes, 12 months ."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1663, "question": "Many facts suggest that children are overweight and the situation is getting worse, according to the doctors. I feel there are a number of reasons for this. Some people blame the fact that we are surrounded by shops selling unhealthy, fatty foods, such as fried chicken and ice cream, at low prices. This has turned out a whole generation of grown-ups who seldom cook a meal for themselves. If there were fewer of these restaurants, then probably children would buy less take-away food. There is another argument that blames parents for allowing their children to become overweight. I agree with this, because good eating habits begin early in life, long before children start to visit fast food shops. If children are given fried chicken and chocolate rather than healthy food, or are always allowed...\n\nQ: According to the text, what kind of children may eat more unhealthy food?", "options": ["Those who often take exercise.", "Those who often watch television.", "Those who often have meals at home.", "Those who often walk to school."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2905, "question": "Pulling heavy suitcases all day in the summer is hard work, especially when you are a thin 14-year-old boy. That was me in 1940-the youngest and smallest baggage boy at New York City's Pennsylvania Railway Station. After just a few days on the job, I began noticing that the other fellows were overcharging passengers. I'd like to join them, thinking, \"Everyone else is doing it.\" When I got home that night, I told my dad what I wanted to do. \"You give an honest day's work,\" he said, looking at me straight in his eye. \"They are paying you. If they want to do that, you let them do that.\" I followed my dad's advice for the rest of that summer and have lived by his words ever since. Of all the jobs I've had, it was my experience at Pennsylvania Railway Station that has stuck with me. Now I teach...\n\nQ: What does the father's advice imply?", "options": ["It is wrong to give more to the passengers.", "Don't believe them if they are paying you more.", "Don't follow others to overcharge the passengers.", "It is difficult to work hard and live as an honest boy."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2753, "question": "In summer, millions of people will head for the beach.And while the ocean can be a great place to swim and play, it may also be useful in another way.Some scientists think that waves could help make electricity. \"Have you ever been on a surfboard or boat and felt yourself being lifted up by a wave? Or have you jumped in the water and felt the energy as waves crashed over you?\" asked Jamie Taylor of the Wave Energy Group at the University of Edinburgh in Scotland.\"There is certainly a lot of energy in waves.\" Scientists are working on using that energy to make electricity. Most waves are created when winds blow across the ocean.\"The winds start out by making little ripples in the water, but if they keep on blowing , those ripples get bigger and bigger and turn into waves, \"Taylor said.\"Wave...\n\nQ: Which of the following is NOT true?", "options": ["Wave power costs too much money.", "Wave energy creates the same amount of pollution as other energy sources.", "Wave power affects fishing and boat traffic.", "Wave power may affect marine animals."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2227, "question": "A Day of Design Sunday, June 27,2010 9 a. m. ~ 4 p. m. Thomas College Student Center Join us for a free day of fun! A Day of Design will encourage those interested in flowers and design to get in touch with their creative side and get some tips from the experts - Jeff and Scott. Pleas see the schedule below for details about this wonderful opportunity! 9:00 a.m. - 10:30 a.m. Registration for the day runs from 9 a.m. in the Student Center. Later guests will take a tour of the Thomas College campus before the day's events. 10:30 a. m. ~ 12:00 p. m. Jeff and Scott will design more than a dozen arrangements in a variety of sizes and colors and auction will be held and guests will have the opportunity to bid on the flower arrangements. 12:00 p. m. ~ 1:00 p. m. A delightful boxed lunch will be s...\n\nQ: We can learn from the passage that A Day of Design    _    .", "options": ["lasts for eight hours", "is free of charge", "is held annually in July", "is aimed at fashion designers"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 3167, "question": "In his 1930 essay \"Economic Possibilities for Our Grandchildren \", John Keynes, a famous economist, wrote that human needs fall into two classes: absolute needs ,which are independent of what others have , and relative needs ,which make us feel superior to our fellows. He thought that although relative needs may indeed be insatiable , this is not true of absolute needs. Keynes was surely correct that only a small part of total spending is decided by the desire for superiority. He was greatly mistaken, however, in seeing this desire as the only source of insatiable demands. Decisions to spend are also driven by ideas of quality which can influence the demands for almost all goods, including even basic goods like food. When a couple goes out for an anniversary dinner, for example, the though...\n\nQ: The author of the passage argues that   _  .", "options": ["absolute needs have no limits", "demands for quality are not insatiable", "human desires influence ideas of quality", "relative needs decide most of our spending"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1353, "question": "A jobless man applied for the position of \"office boy\" at Microsoft. The HR manager interviewed him and then watched him cleaning the floor as a test. \"You are employed,\" he said. \"Give me your e-mail address and I'll send you the application to fill in, as well as date when you may start. \" The man replied, \"But I don't have a computer, neither an e-mail. \" \"I'm sorry,\" said the HR manager. \"If you don't have an e-mail, that means you do not exist. And who doesn't exist cannot have the job. \" The man left with no hope at all. He didn't know what to do, with only ten dollars in his pocket. He then decided to go to the supermarket and buy 10kg tomatoes. He then sold the tomatoes from door to door. In less than two hours, he succeeded to double his capital. He repeated the operation three ti...\n\nQ: Which proverb can best describe the story?", "options": ["Misfortune may be an actual blessing.", "Where there is a will, there is a way.", "Accidents will happen.", "No pains , no gains."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2797, "question": "There are many acceptable varieties of English throughout the world. Whichever variety is used in your country, the most important thing is that students' pronunciation must be good enough for another person to understand what they are trying to say. In a PPP lesson, teachers naturally include a good model of the pronunciation when they are presenting new vocabulary, grammar or functional language. It is important to start by helping your students recognize sounds before you expect them to produce them. Spoken British English has 44 sounds, but there are only 26 letters in the alphabet for written English. This sometimes makes English pronunciation and spelling different, so it is not always best to write words on the blackboard at the early stages. Also, some sounds in English do not exis...\n\nQ: In the author's opinion,   _  .", "options": ["it is not necessary to pronounce every word correctly", "the English phonetic alphabet is a must in teaching pronunciation", "students should pronounce every word as precisely as native speakers", "pronunciation means more than knowing how to pronounce every single word"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2658, "question": "Along a long path we came to a deep valley, on the far side of which the path led into some very thick bushes. Rather than push through up again and rejoin the path on the far side of the bushes As I climbed down into the valley a bird flew off h rock on which I had put my hand. On looking at the spot from which the bird had risen, I saw two eggs. They were the kind that I did not have in my collection, so I placed them carefully in my bag, wrapped in a little dry grass. As we went further down the valley the sides became steeper and not far from where I had entered. It came to drop of about twelve to fourteen feet. The water that rushed down all these small valleys in the rainy season had worn the rock as glass. As it was too deep to climb down, I handed my gun to one of the men and slid ...\n\nQ: According to the text we know that   _", "options": ["the writer decided to push through the thick bushes", "the writer decided to walk along the valley", "the writer wanted to stop climbing", "the writer tried to find two eggs"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2318, "question": "Where and how you eat are just as important as what you eat. Take this test to find your eating style to make sure you're getting the nutrition you need. Which statements sound like you? Group 1: # I like to make my plate look pretty before I dig in for the first bite. # I often help my parents make recipes. # I could win the first prize in the \"World's Slowest Eater\" contest. Group 2: # The crumbs in the sofa are mine -- I eat while watching TV. # I can finish a whole box of snacks quickly while I'm doing something else. # Sometimes I'm surprised to find my plate empty. Where did all the food go? Group 3: # Sometimes I eat my dinner standing up. # I spend more time in the drive-through than at the dinner table. # Breakfast? Who has time for breakfast? If you answered mostly Group 1: You e...\n\nQ: Which of the following matches Group 1?", "options": ["I like washing plates.", "I love buying cookers.", "I enjoy doing cooking by myself.", "I do everything slowly and carefully."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2492, "question": "Actress Hayden Panettiere recently got into trouble with Japanese fishermen as she tried to stop them from killing dolphins. The 18-year-old star with some other surfers sailed out to reach the dolphins in order to stop them from being driven into a nearby pool and killed, but the six surfers, from Australia and the United States, were stopped by a fishing boat before they could reach them. The fishermen blocked their way with a boathook . It was an ugly, unfriendly and life-threatening struggle before the surfers were forced to return to the beach. It is believed that the dolphins were later taken into a pool and killed. Panettiere, who is a brave surfer and loyal animal protector, made up her mind to save the dolphins of Japan and said, \"It was really frightening. Some of us were hit by ...\n\nQ: Which of the following would be the best title for this passage?", "options": ["What Happened While Surfing in Japan", "Hayden Panettiere Cried in the Sea of Japan", "People Worldwide Are Against Killing Dolphins", "Protect the Wild Animals"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 3345, "question": "People with disabilities make up a large part of the population. It is estimated that over 35 million Americans have physical, mental, or other disabilities. About half of these disabilities are \"developmental\", i.e., they occur before the individual's twenty-second birthday, often from genetic conditions, and are severe enough to affect three or more areas of development, such as mobility, communication, employment, etc. Most other disabilities are considered \"adventitious\", i.e., accidental or caused by outside forces. Prior to the 20th century, only a small percentage of people with disabilities survived for long. Medical treatment for these disabilities was unavailable. Advancements in medicine and social services have created a climate in which people with disabilities can expect to h...\n\nQ: Which of the following cannot be inferred from the passage ?", "options": ["Many disabled people may remain single for their whole life.", "The public tends to look down upon the disabled people.", "The disabled people feel inferior to those surrounding them.", "Discriminatory laws prevent the disabled from mixing with others."], "answer": 3}]